<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Aloe Records</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Aloe Records</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2022, Aloe Records.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 04:28:24 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Alone-002: Yan Jun - it works</title>
      <link>/releases/alone-002/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 04:28:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/releases/alone-002/</guid>
      <description>Simple block structures, great dynamics with great noise, and perhaps a little mystery to it. Alone002 new cassette release “it works” is a conceptual collection of works by Beijing, China based musician/poet Yan Jun, from one live improvisation to two performance recordings composed by Ryoko Akama. &amp;ldquo;sometimes people concern if one piece of work good enough. or more detailed, is it a pleasure of listening? or is it unique? sometimes also argue &amp;ldquo;is it art/music or not&amp;rdquo;, or what kind of music is it and what kind of standard we should apply to value it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alone-001: Zhu Wenbo - Four Lines and Improvisation</title>
      <link>/releases/alone-001/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 04:15:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/releases/alone-001/</guid>
      <description>Alone Series 001 is absolutely delighted to release a new album by Beijing, China-based musician Zhu Wenbo, entitled &amp;ldquo;Four Lines and Improvisation&amp;rdquo;, recorded in August 2022. Zhu Wenbo is a multi-instrumentalist and composer who is dedicated to &amp;ldquo;music that doesn&amp;rsquo;t sound like music&amp;rdquo;. He also runs the label Zoomin’ Night. The album contains two tracks: ”Four Lines”(A-side) and “Improvisation”(B), released in one limited edition cassette. Both tracks naturally showcase the Lo-Fi nature of experimental composition/electro-acoustic improvisation that has always been a hallmark of Zhu Wenbo&amp;rsquo;s work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A small matter to tell you about</title>
      <link>/blog/a-small-matter-to-tell/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2022 04:40:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/a-small-matter-to-tell/</guid>
      <description>Author: Sun Yizhou
English Translation: Zhang Cai
Proofread: Rania Ho
I shall start from the recent past.
Shit happened in 2022—quite a lot, in Beijing in particular. Each morning you and I woke up petrified, drawn into some fucked-up incident through social media, insulted by someone for some matter that was by then sealed, closed and inaccessible. Incomprehensible at first, we erupted into a fury; in the end, all we could do was sit and complain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Aloe Records Aloe Records(芦荟唱片) , a Beijing-based limited edition publishing label. Focusing primarily on electro-acoustic improvisation, experimental composition, post-2000 improvised music, conceptual sound works, and more radical or obscure sound practices. Run by Sun Yizhou since 2022.
It is currently self-operated and its publications are not limited to any medium. The aim is to gradually build an international network for contemporary musicians and sound artists, conceptual artists, media artists and performance artists.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/contact/</guid>
      <description>Contact For demos, we prefer to invite artists and not accepting demos at this time, thanks.
For purchases, digital versions/single physical publications are available on bandcamp. For more volume of physical publications, or if you wish to support us, please feel free to contact us.
Email: aloerecordss@gmail.com</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
