<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Releases on Aloe Records</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/releases/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Releases on Aloe Records</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2022, Aloe Records.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 09:41:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/releases/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Alone-006: Roel Meelkop - Muddy Ponds</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/releases/0370/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 09:41:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/releases/0370/</guid>
      <description>Muddy Ponds is a pretty uncommon work, unlike any of his former releases. The context is basically one of frustration, of unclarity. Thus it’s fuller and muddier than usual, hence the title.&#xA;“Near my house there is a natural pond and in springtime and summer it&amp;rsquo;s full of frogs talking to each other. I love the sounds they make, so I decided to make a recording of this. Afterwards, when I listened to it, I noticed how many other sounds were present as well, which meant I had no clean recording of the frogs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> Alone-005: Leo Okagawa - Send and Return</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/releases/0307/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 09:34:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/releases/0307/</guid>
      <description>This is Leo Okagawa&amp;rsquo;s live solo electronic album, respectively, at Nanahari 七針, located in Tokyo, and Center, located in kunama, Tochigi. And he went like he&amp;rsquo;s sending and returning from the same place.&#xA;Leo Okagawa interview on the website.&#xA;English: aloerecords.com/blog/0202/&#xA;Chinese: aloerecords.com/blog/0217/&#xA;• 250g front and back printing paper.&#xA;• professional transparent cassette &amp;amp; digital download code.&#xA;• handwritten number.&#xA;• Only 40 copies!&#xA;Solo performance at Center, Tochigi, Japan on July 8, 2023</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alone-004: Zhao Cong - 55355</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/releases/0923/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 06:13:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/releases/0923/</guid>
      <description>55355 is a recording that is both outdoors and in-outdoors at the same time. It is &amp;ldquo;electric&amp;rdquo; music, but not electronic music at the same time. Recorded on 9th April 2023, it consists of four sessions, which were excerpted after without overdubbing. This may sound cryptic, but would make clear once you hear it.&#xA;• 220g front and back printing paper. • professional transparent flash cassette &amp;amp; digital download code.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alone-003: Grisha Shakhnes - here</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/releases/0922/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 06:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/releases/0922/</guid>
      <description>Grisha Shakhnes is a composer and sound artist currently living in Israel. He moved to a new place in Holon in 2022, in which he have it recorded for the first time, as simple as the title suggests. Here is a place that looks out to the rear. With the windows open in his guest room, he uses analog tape samples during the creativity. From empty to full. You will hear things appear and disappear in various proportions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aloe-002: Luke Martin / Noah Ophoven-Baldwin - aperture</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/releases/aloe-002-luke-martin-noah-ophoven-baldwin-aperture/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 16:04:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/releases/aloe-002-luke-martin-noah-ophoven-baldwin-aperture/</guid>
      <description>Track 1: &amp;ldquo;all the rooms of light&amp;rdquo; (31:00), Noah Ophoven-Baldwin Luke Martin - no-input mixing board &amp;amp; electric guitar Noah Ophoven-Baldwin - cornet Track 2: &amp;ldquo;an inconsistent latency&amp;rdquo; (40:50), Luke Martin Luke Martin - electric guitar Noah Ophoven-Baldwin - cornet Minneapolis, USA, August 2022 Recorded by Patrick Marschke Mixed by Luke Martin Mastered by Hiroyuki Ura Released by Aloe Records 2023 (Aloe-002) www.aloerecords.com&#xA;-&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;- The new album &amp;ldquo;aperture&amp;rdquo; is a collaboration between two Minneapolis-based composers and performers, Luke Martin and Noah Ophoven-Baldwin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aloe-001: Soviet Pop - two small works: continuous and discrete</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/releases/aloe-001/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 15:39:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/releases/aloe-001/</guid>
      <description>Track A: Op. 1 19’34’’&#xA;Track B: Op. 2 19’32’’&#xA;All sounds come from Soviet Pop 苏维埃波普&#xA;Snare Drum (A) Pedal cymbal (B) by Li Qing 李青&#xA;Metronome (B) Four-track tape recorder (A&amp;amp;B) by Li Weisi 李维思&#xA;Recorded on March 24, 2023, Beijing&#xA;Mastered by Hiroyuki Ura 浦裕幸&#xA;Cover art origin from René Daniëls 勒内·丹尼尔斯&#xA;Designed by Cai 爫&#xA;Released by Aloe Records 2023 (Aloe-001)&#xA;www.aloerecords.com&#xA;-&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;- Aloe Series (Aloe Record&amp;rsquo;s new series for duos) is pleased to present a new album by Soviet Pop, an electronic-acoustic duo consisting of Li Qing and Li Weisi, who are also members of well-known indie rock bands.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alone-002: Yan Jun - it works</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/releases/alone-002/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 04:28:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/releases/alone-002/</guid>
      <description>Simple block structures, great dynamics with great noise, and perhaps a little mystery to it. Alone002 new cassette release “it works” is a conceptual collection of works by Beijing, China based musician/poet Yan Jun, from one live improvisation to two performance recordings composed by Ryoko Akama. &amp;ldquo;sometimes people concern if one piece of work good enough. or more detailed, is it a pleasure of listening? or is it unique? sometimes also argue &amp;ldquo;is it art/music or not&amp;rdquo;, or what kind of music is it and what kind of standard we should apply to value it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alone-001: Zhu Wenbo - Four Lines and Improvisation</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/releases/alone-001/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 04:15:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/releases/alone-001/</guid>
      <description>Alone Series 001 is absolutely delighted to release a new album by Beijing, China-based musician Zhu Wenbo, entitled &amp;ldquo;Four Lines and Improvisation&amp;rdquo;, recorded in August 2022. Zhu Wenbo is a multi-instrumentalist and composer who is dedicated to &amp;ldquo;music that doesn&amp;rsquo;t sound like music&amp;rdquo;. He also runs the label Zoomin’ Night. The album contains two tracks: ”Four Lines”(A-side) and “Improvisation”(B), released in one limited edition cassette. Both tracks naturally showcase the Lo-Fi nature of experimental composition/electro-acoustic improvisation that has always been a hallmark of Zhu Wenbo&amp;rsquo;s work.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
